更多精彩关注 @NeverKeepingItReal
翻译  暴龙蛋  西西  猎魔章鱼X
翻译  吃西瓜不吐皮  Reginamoon  红枫Gabriel
翻译  DustDevil  milkon  胖兔纯
时间轴 姜姜 今  suki      校对 胖兔纯
后期   蜡笔小新的眉毛      总监  胖兔纯
康斯坦丁
康
斯
坦
丁
康斯坦丁
第一季   第十集
把灵魂交给我[拉丁语]
Eripe animam,
血液全归于我[拉丁语]
flere sanguine venire
我将...[拉丁语]
ad me, et ponam
赐你安睡[拉丁语]
te in somnum.
睡觉也要打扮得美美的哦  特里西娅
Can't get pretty sleep without looking pretty, Tricia.
你先等着  一会我也会给你打扮得美美的
Now wait your turn and I'll make you pretty, too.
我在房子周围施放了一个障眼法
I cast a duplicity spell around the perimeter of the property.
从现在开始  任何寻找磨坊的人
From now on, anyone searching for the mill house
最终都只会离磨坊
will find themselves on a path leading away
越来越远
from the mill house.
这个地方现在安全了  泽德
This place is safe now, Zed.
我之前也是那么想的  但他们还是找到了我
That's what I thought before, but they still found me.
他们是谁
And who are they?
听着  之前你闭口不提你的过去
Look, you kept your cards close about your past
我都尊重你的意思  但现在不行了
and I chose not to push, but I am pushing now.
他们自称为圣临十字军
They call themselves the Resurrection Crusade.
他们要你做什么
And what do they want with you?
他们就是疯子
They're fanatics.
全然相信他们首领对于未来的预见
Completely bent on their leader's vision of the future.
而那个首领
And-and he-- the-the leader?
他认为我是那个未来的关键
He believes I'm crucial to the vision.
这么说你是被一群狂热邪教份子盯上了
So you found yourself in the crosshairs of a delusional cult.
他们自己可不是这么认为的
In their minds, they're... they're much more.
我必须得躲起来
And I need to disappear.
这次我非走不可了
And this time I need to stay gone.
如果你真要找地方躲起来
If you need to disappear...
这里再适合不过了
best place to do it is here.
你的那些保护措施根本不够
All the protections you've used-- they're not enough.
他不找到我是不会甘休的
He'll never stop searching for me.
你连地狱的恶魔都毫不畏惧
You're yet to flinch in the face of the underworld.
为什么你这么怕他
Why are you so afraid of a man from this one?
因为他是我父亲
Because he's my father.
我才不管他是不是你的父亲
Well, I don't care if he's the heavenly bloody father,
亲爱的  他得先过了我这关
luv, he ain't getting past me.
为什么要帮我  你为什么相信我
Why do you want to help me? Why do you believe me?
我这人向来靠直觉
I survive on instinct.
我的直觉告诉我你信得过
Mine tells me that you're all right.
再说了  你怎么着也算是个美人
It doesn't hurt that you're easy on the eyes, as well.
我也希望能这么跟你说
Wish I could say the same.
真是谢了啊
Oh, thanks.
纽约州
约翰
Hey, John.
地图上又出现了血迹
The scry map-- it's bleeding again.
这回轮到纽约市这大苹果了
Painting the Big Apple red.
查斯这周要去看女儿
It's Chas's weekend with his daughter.
他这会应该已经在去布鲁克林的路上了
He's on his way to Brooklyn right now.
那我去订机票
I'll book our flights.
*宝贝  牵着我的手*
*Baby, take my hand*
*别害怕死神*
*Don't fear the reaper*
*我们很快就能飞翔*
*We'll be able to fly*
*别害怕死神*
*Don't fear the reaper*
*宝贝  我是你的男人*
*Baby, I'm your man...*
你穿着我喜欢的那件蓝色情趣内衣吗
Hey, you wearing that blue teddy I like?
你觉得我穿上很好看吗
You like the way it looks on me?
不  蕾妮
No, Renee.
我觉得扒掉它更好看
I like the way it looks on the floor.
杰拉尔汀还等着你回家哄她睡觉呢
Geraldine's waiting for you to tuck her in.
我也等着你呢  你什么时候回家
I'm next in line. When are you coming home?
现在就回
Right now, baby.
我们走吧  亲爱的  没错  就这样
Let's get out of here, luv. All right, that's lovely.
查斯
Hey, Chas.
查斯  查斯  我得走了
Chas, Chas, I've got to go.
我钓到一个妞  你买单好吗
I've got a bird. So pick up the tab, yeah?
上一次还有上上次都是我买的单
I picked up the last tab and the one before that.
那我下两次  下三次都我买好了
Yeah, but I'll get the next, um... two. Three.
-走吧  -等我一会儿
- Go. Go. - Listen, just give me a second.
一会就好
One second.
你开车没问题吧
Are you sure you're all right to drive?
我没事
Yeah, I'm-I'm fine.
你骗人
You're a liar.
[咒语]
很好  谢谢你
Oh, good, thank you. Yeah.
现在你没问题了
Now you're okay.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎百合与斧乐队
Lillian Axe!
那些烟火把东西烧着了
The pyrotechnics are causing a fire!
起火了
Fire!
快点  都出去
Come on, back up!
起火了  快逃啊
Fire! Clear out!
太多人挡住门口了
There's too many bodies blocking the door!
小心
Look out.
*别害怕死神*
*Don't fear the reaper*
当地新闻已经有报道了  看
It's already hit the local news. Look.
布鲁克林大概有十二个人
About a dozen people in Brooklyn
陷入了无法解释的昏迷中
have fallen into unexplained comas.
黑暗崛起的力量日益增强
As the Rising Darkness grows,
它的目标也越来越多
so will its targets.
布鲁克林只是个开始
Brooklyn will be just the beginning.
你不是要简装出发吗  只带点必需品
I thought you were packing light, only the essentials.
这些就是必需品
Which is what it is.
这是阿莱斯特·克劳利的东西
This belonged to Aleister Crowley.
当我不知从何下手的时候
When I haven't a clue where to begin on a case,
它能帮我找到头绪
helps me know where to start.
这是什么
What is this?
我的手麻了
My-my hand's numb.
查斯最爱的玩意儿
Chas's favorite trick--
阿喀琉斯脚踝的肌腱
sinew from Achilles' heel.
它对魔法免疫
Impervious to magic.
世上最有韧性的东西
Highest tinsel strength on this world or any other.
我以为阿喀琉斯的脚踝是他的死穴
I thought Achilles' heel was weak.
现在你知道为什么了  走吧
Well, now you know why. Let's go.
她撑不住睡着了
She stayed up as long as she could.
我给她买了这个  我去看看她是不是还醒着
Well, I-I bought this for her. I'm gonna go see if she's awake.
我一个小时前抱她上楼了
I carried her up an hour ago.
至少让我替她掖掖被子吧
You could've at least let me tuck her in.
你抱怨说总见不到女儿
You complain that you never get to see your daughter,
但每个能来探视的周末
but then you're late every weekend,
你却总是迟到  弗兰西斯
you have custody, Francis.
我请求过你了  别这么叫我  蕾妮
I've nicely asked you not to call me that, Renee.
你为什么又晚了
Why are you late?
宝贝  你还醒着吗
Sweetie, you awake?
蕾妮
Renee!
杰拉尔汀  宝贝
Geraldine, baby.
还是不接电话
Still no answer.
查斯留言里说了什么
What did Chas say in his message?
该说的都说了
Everything he had to.
他需要我们
That he needs us here.
伙计  我们尽快赶来了
Came as fast we could, mate.
出了什么事
So, what's the story?
我只放心把她交给你  约翰
You're the only one I'd trust with her, John.
不管发生什么
Well, whatever this is, mate,
我们都会陪你一起解决
we're in it with you, all right?
所以
So...
能跟我们说说事情经过吗
you want to tell us what happened?
我发现她倒在地上流血不止  就赶紧把她送来医院
I found her on the floor bleeding. We raced here,
我看见还有六个患者也有相同症状
I saw six other patients with the same symptoms.
他们说是昏迷  可这不像我见过的
They're calling it a coma, but this isn't like any coma
任何一种昏迷
I've ever seen.
她是我女儿  我应该
She's my daughter, I should...
-在她身边保护她的  -你也不知道
- should've been here for her. - There's no way
她会遇上这种事  查斯
you could've known she was in trouble, Chas.
她的嘴唇裂开了
Her lips are chapped.
这是天火焚烧的痕迹
Celestial burn marks.
当灵魂离体的时候就会留下这种痕迹
Left behind when a soul departs.
所以这只是杰拉尔汀的躯体
This is just Geraldine's body?
至少还活着  是个好事
Alive and breathing, which is the good news.
那坏事是什么
And the bad?
这个...
Well...
如果她的灵魂被用于黑暗用途  那么
if her soul is being used for a dark purpose, then
她没多少时间可活了  最多一两天吧
she doesn't have long-- a day or two at most.
-怎么才能把灵魂和肉体分离  -分不了
- How can you separate a soul from a body? - You don't.
这是黑魔法的最高境界
It's the, uh, Holy Grail of black magic.
许多凡人试过  但无一成功
Many a mortal have tried and failed.
我要你不惜一切代价救回她  约翰
Promise me you'll do whatever it takes to get her back, John.
那你得先保证  你要完全照我说的做
You promise me that you'll do everything I tell you.
谢谢
Thank you.
客气  大兄弟
All right, big man.
我有个老朋友  以前曾是灵媒
I have an old friend who used to be a medium.
他可以联系到杰拉尔汀
He can contact Geraldine.
但愿她能告诉我们她在哪
Hopefully she can tell us where she is.
不过我需要一件  她的个人物品
I just need, uh, one of her personal belongings.
没事的  宝贝
It's okay, sweetheart.
我会好好保管它的
She's in good hands.
行吧
Yeah.
他在这干什么
What's he doing here?
约翰是来帮忙的
John's here for support.
你好  蕾妮
Hello, Renee.
我是泽德
I'm Zed.
给你个建议
Piece of advice?
不管他出了门往哪走  你最好跟他分道扬镳
Whichever way he goes out that door, you go the other.
我们在外面等
We'll be right outside.
跟我说实话
Tell me the truth.
他来干什么
Why is he here?
他会想尽办法救回杰拉尔汀
'Cause he'll do whatever it takes to save Geraldine.
就像纽卡斯尔那次一样吗
What, like he saved that girl in Newcastle?
我不知道你为什么这么盲目地跟着他
I don't know why you follow him around so blindly,
但别让他碰我们的女儿
but keep him away from our daughter.
爸爸
Daddy.
查斯
Chas?
我的天  查斯  你
Oh, my God, Chas, you're...
我还以为我再也见不到你了
I thought I was never gonna see you again.
我就在这呢  爸爸
But I've been right here, Daddy.
他们把你从火场救出来的时候
God, they told us that you were dead
就告诉我们你没救了
when they pulled you out of that fire.
我当时在救一个女孩
I was helping a girl escape.
我是该活不成的
I should be dead.
但你活下来了
Oh, you're alive now.
这就够了
That's all that matters.
军品专卖
那个灵媒就住这
This is the medium's place?
你的朋友还真是三教九流啊  约翰
You got friends in low places, John.
进去吧
Come on.
赶牛棒
Cattle prod?
怎么了  我一直想买一个
What? I've always wanted one.
不是吧
Really?
哪有灵媒卖军品的
What kind of medium works at an Army surplus store?
有妄想症的就会
A paranoid one.
你好啊  菲内尔
Hello, Fennel.
我说什么来着
Told you.
-滚出我的店  -我还以为你们是朋友
- Get your ass out of my store. - I thought you were friends.
显然有人把友谊给忘了
Apparently, one of us has forgotten.
有个女孩的灵魂被偷了
A girl's soul has been stolen.
我们需要你来联系她
We need you to help us contact her.
你身边站着的是个骗子和小偷
You walked in here with a liar and a thief.
不管你说什么
You can ask all you want,
我都绝不会帮助约翰·康斯坦丁的
I'll never help John Constantine.
你不帮不行
We're not asking.
看来好东西都藏在这呢
Take it this is where the good stuff's kept.
你做得好  我就欠你一个大人情
You do this right, I'll be in your debt,
我的人情可不是说着玩的
and that's no small fee.
我可以给你接点干净水
I can get you some clean water.
这是约旦河水
It's from the River Jordan.
能使交流过程更顺畅
Acts like a lubricant for communication.
我一给你信号  你就把布娃娃给我
I give you the signal, you give me the doll.
都听你的  哥们
It's your show, mate.
[咒语]
她来了
She's with us now.
别打断联系
Don't break the connection.
杰拉尔汀  我会救你回来的
Geraldine, I'm gonna get you back.
坚持住  宝贝
You just hold on, baby.
爸爸  这是怎么回事
Daddy, what's happening?
我是约翰叔叔  亲爱的
It's your Uncle John, luv.
你身边有别人吗
Is there anyone with you?
没有  就我一个人  我很害怕
No, I'm alone. I'm scared.
没事的  宝贝  你看看周围
It's all right, sweetheart. Now, I need you to look around.
告诉我你看到了什么
Tell me what you see.
我看到...我看到...
I see... I see...
谁胆敢跟我偷走的灵魂说话
Who dares speak to one of my stolen souls?
她去哪了  怎么回事
Where'd she go?! What's happening?!
有人控制了菲内尔
Someone's taken control of Fennel,
很明显不是杰拉尔汀
and it certainly isn't Geraldine.
是你吗  约翰·康斯坦丁
Oh, is that you, John Constantine?
好久不见
It's been a long time.
自报家门
Identify yourself.
像真男人一样面对我
Face me like a real man,
而不是躲在别人身体里跟个木偶似的
not with your hand up another's ass like a bloody puppet.
这事你管不了的
It's more than you can do.
很抱歉我没时间浪费在你这种人身上
I'm sorry I don't have time to waste on your likes.
告诉我你是谁
Tell me who you are.
我警告过你了  康斯坦丁
You've been warned, Constantine.
为你们的主人[拉丁语]
Et stabit de domino
站出来  所有人[拉丁语]
vestro, aliquis.
为你们的主人站出来[拉丁语]
Et stabit de domino vestro.
听我号令[拉丁语]
Audite vocem meam.
我们的降神被另一个法师强行控制了
Our seance was hijacked by another mage.
他用了一个强大的咒语
He used a powerful spell,
把菲内尔烧成灰烬了
turned Fennel into a bloody crisp.
他说出了你的名字  他认识你
He said your name. He knew you.
是的  我们都知道  这不是什么好事
Yes, admittedly, not a good thing,
但他确实说了好久不见
but he did say it had been a long time.
我们这完全是在浪费时间
And all we've done is waste ours.
你对我承诺过的
You made me a promise.
我也准备信守这个承诺  查斯
It's a promise that I aim to keep, Chas.
我们距找出
We're one step closer
劫走你女儿的人又近了一步
to finding the man that's holding your daughter hostage.
只有五本书上记载了这个咒语
Only five books contain this spell,
而这些书都被一位爱尔兰高王分散在世界各地
each scattered across the globe by an Irish High King.
如果我们能找到距离最近的那本书...
Now, if we can find the location of the nearest book...
就能找到杰拉尔汀
We find Geraldine.
正是
Exactly.
让我摸摸咒语
Let me hold the spell.
你在哪
Where are you?
废弃的火车厂  或是...
Dusty rail yard or...
实验室
laboratory.
我也说不好
Um, I'm not sure.
我看到有大锅
I see cauldrons
很多书  还有火车
and books and a train car.
找找标识  标语
Look for a sign, a placard,
任何能让给你信息的东西
anything that can give you a name.
哈斯金斯火车厂
"Haskins Railroad Yard."
你看到杰拉尔汀了吗
Do you see Geraldine?
没有
No.
看起来就我一个人
It looks like I'm all alone.
过来  让我看看
Here. Let me look at that.
看来那人法力高强  这是我不想见到的
Someone out there has more power than I care to chance upon.
告诉我发生了什么
Tell me what happened.
有一阵打旋的蒸汽
There was a swirling vapor
从我身边飘过  我一转身
that drifted past me. When I turned around,
一个穿斗篷的男人
there was a man in a cloak,
拿着刀冲向了我
and he lunged at me with a knife.
坩埚和书籍  斗篷和匕首
Cauldrons and books, cloaks and daggers.
可能是炼金术士  或者疯掉的魔法师
Could be some sort of alchemist or a mage gone mad.
他长什么样  描述给我听
What did he look like? Describe him to me.
冷静  查斯  让她喘口气
Easy, Chas. Just let her breathe.
别让我冷静
Don't tell me easy.
我想知道夺走我女儿的男人长什么样子
I want to know what the man who has my daughter looks like.
我们去见见他吧  怎样
Let's go and see for ourselves, shall we?
你是说哈斯金斯火车厂吗
Haskins Railroad Yard, you say?
-是的  -那好吧
- Yeah. - All right, then.
我们去看看
Let's check it out.
电话簿上写的就是这地址
According to the phone book, this is the address.
我打电话给交通局了
I called the Transit Authority.
他们说哈斯金斯火车厂几年前就关了
They said Haskins Railroad Yard was shut down years ago.
又是死胡同  这简直是在浪费时间
More dead ends, more wasted time.
我听说百分之九十的真相都源于直觉
I've heard it said that nine- tenths of reality is perception,
而在我看来  是百分之一百二十
and in my trade, it's eleven-tenths.
你瞧
Ah, you see?
假如一位法师
If a mage
不能完全改变你对真实的感知
can't completely change your idea of what's real,
那么...他的把戏就不起作用了
well, then... the trick don't work.
那东西哪去了
Where'd it go?
世间五行元素  吾虔诚召唤汝
Five elements of the earth, I respect and invoke thee.
源于六方  皆汇于此
From the six directions, converge here.
揭示真相  显露真身
Lift all concealments, reveal thy truth.
这是隐形的
It was invisible.
是用了障眼法  还是初级的那种
By way of a cloaking spell, and an elementary one at that.
无论住在这里的是谁
But whatever taking up residence here
绝对不是什么好人
certainly harbors a dark side.
他们还没见识到我的黑暗面
They haven't met mine.
我预感到了你要来
I had a feeling you'd come.
我甚至暗地里希望你会来
I think I even hoped you would.
你对那个女孩的灵魂做了什么
What have you done with the girl's soul?
你得说得更具体一些
You'll have to be more specific.
我的听力大不如前了
My hearing isn't what it used to be.
泽德
Zed,
来见见菲力克斯·浮士德
Meet Felix Faust,
他给当代最厉害的黑魔法师
lifetime apprentice and second fiddle
当了一辈子的学徒和副手
to the greatest black magicians of his generation.
的确是副手  康斯坦丁
Second fiddle indeed, Constantine.
魔法师不过是照本宣科  我却是创造者
The mages played the melody, but I wrote the concerto.
他们不过是站在我的肩膀上取得成就的
They built their legends on my shoulders.
去别处宣传你这论调吧  菲力克斯
Spin your tune someplace else, Felix,
领我去见你的主子
and point me to your master.
这是我一人所为  没别人
This is my doing, no one else's.
我一辈子都在服侍别人
I spent a lifetime serving others.
如今我只为自己
Now I serve only myself.
他说的是实话  约翰
He's telling the truth, John.
他不过是一位垂垂老矣的法师
He's a geriatric spell caster,
追逐着遥不可及的辉煌成就
chasing a prime that never was.
我以一己之力发现了将灵魂与身体分离的方法
I alone discovered how to separate soul from body,
而那些灵魂给予了我更多的力量
and those souls have given me more power
这是当代任何魔法师都做不到的
than any magician of the modern age.
其中一个灵魂是我女儿的
One of those souls belongs to my daughter.
-我要夺回来  -不行
- I'm taking it back! - No!
住手  浮士德
That's enough, Faust!
我说了  住手
I said, that's enough!
你告诉我...
You tell me...
你想要什么
what do you want?
我想要你来侍奉我
I want you to serve me.
一个名叫魇魔的凶残恶魔
A malignant demon named Karabasan is
正在猎食我的猎物
preying on my victims,
吸取属于我的力量
siphoning powers that belong to me.
既然有你供我指使  我就没必要以身试险了
I see no reason to endanger myself when I have you at my beckoning.
把那寄生虫赶回地狱
Cast the parasite to hell,
我就放了那女孩
and I'll free the girl.
他在撒谎吗  约翰
Is he lying, John?
天资卓越  有诚信的法师
One talented and honorable mage
是绝不会对自己的同类撒谎的
would never lie to another.
以大法师德狄之名
In the name of Dedi of Djed-Sneferu.
誓言永存
He who endures.
那个肮脏的恶魔在哪里
Where is the demonic bottom-feeder dwelling?
在红钩区的一处废弃仓库里
In an abandoned warehouse in Red Hook.
为了他女儿  我建议你们...
And for the sake of his daughter, I suggest
在他来找你之前...
you find him...
你先找到他
before he finds you.
我们为什么要走
Why are we leaving?
只要魔法师一死  他的咒语就会失效
If a magician dies, his spells are broken.
我们杀了他吧
Let's kill him.
你感受过拥有那些灵魂的他有多强大了
You felt what he can do with those souls in his pocket.
在我们找出他的弱点之前  得先照他的规则来玩
We play his game until we can find an advantage.
你什么时候开始害怕菲力克斯·浮士德了
Since when do you run from Felix Faust?
上次见到他时  你在地狱厨房跟他玩扑克
The last time we saw him, you were taking his gin money
还把他的酒钱都赢光了
in a Hell's Kitchen poker game.
可他现在比我更强了
Now he's bloody stronger than me.
这都是黑暗崛起导致的
That's the problem with the Rising Darkness.
甚至像浮士德这样的废物
Even a relic like Faust
也能在一夜之间变得充满威胁
can become lethal overnight.
我们会想尽办法救她出来的  查斯
We'll keep doing all we can, Chas.
我们现在做的还不够
What we're doing isn't enough.
她的时间不多了
She doesn't have much time.
你答应过我的  约翰
You promised me, John.
你也答应过我你什么都会听我的
And you promised me you'd do exactly as I said.
当你攻击浮士德时
You know, when you attacked Faust,
你该庆幸他没有动手抹杀杰拉尔汀的灵魂
you're lucky that he didn't snuff out Geraldine's soul in spite.
那个老头终于得到了这么多年来
That old man finally has the power
他梦寐以求的力量
that he's always yearned for.
这人狠毒狡诈  还暴躁偏激
He's vicious and impulsive,
杀死他的唯一办法
and the only way to kill him
就是打破他的防御
is to get inside his defenses.
在此之前  我们得照他说的做以等待时机
And until we do that, we bide our time and we do as he says.
现在去医院吧
Now, go to the hospital.
陪着蕾妮
Be with Renee.
你不能赶查斯走
You can't ask Chas to leave now.
不能吗
Oh, can't I?
我们已经害得一个人送命了
We already left behind one dead body,
他本不该死的
didn't deserve what he got.
我们需要头脑清醒的人
We need clear heads.
不是你走  就是我走
You go or I go.
我了解他比对我自己都更了解
I know that man better than I know myself.
他就是个火药桶
He's a bloody powder keg.
他要爆发的时候我们最好离远点
We don't want to be anywhere near him when he blows.
魇魔可不是个好对付的
Karabasan's a nasty bugger.
专对熟睡的受害者下手  麻痹他们的身体
Preys on sleeping victims, paralyzing their bodies
吃掉他们的内脏  夺走他们的生命
as it dines on their innards and sucks their life away.
菲力克斯那些昏迷的受害者们
Felix's coma victims
就是他送上门的大餐
are a meal ready to eat.
我们帮浮士德驱逐了魇魔
Won't banishing Karabasan
不是只会让他更强大吗
only make Faust stronger?
短期内是的
For the short term, yes,
但这能保住杰拉尔汀的性命
but it keeps Geraldine alive,
给我们争取到想出应对计划的时间
gives us a chance to figure out a plan.
我们得让那个恶魔被困在魔法阵里足够长时间
We need the scourge held in the circle long enough
这样我才能将它赶回地狱
so I can order it to hell.
当魇魔进入这里  我们立刻退到魔法阵外
When Karabasan enters, we'll retreat behind this circle line.
只要它一走进来
When he steps inside...
它唯一的去处就是地狱
the only place he's going is down.
我们不能在这里和它玩捉迷藏了
We can't play hide-and-seek with it in here.
这地方就是个迷宫
It's a bloody labyrinth.
那我们让它来找我们
Then we'll make it come to us.
47名酒吧火灾遇难者名单公布
我看过了
I saw that.
真是个悲剧
Bloody tragedy.
我们两个真不知道走了什么运
Horseshoes up our asses, you and I.
走得还真是及时
How lucky were we to leave when we did?
我没走
I didn't leave.
那地方被烧毁的时候我在里面
I was there when that building burned down.
这上面说从废墟中找到了47名遇难者
Says there that 47 victims were pulled from the rubble.
那我告诉你  其实是48名
And I'm telling you there were 48.
我身上的烧伤  创伤  骨折
I had burns, injuries, broken bones.
全都痊愈了
All healed.
一夜之间
Overnight.
一定有什么地方不对  约翰
Something isn't right, John.
竟然真的成功了
It bloody worked.
什么成功了
What bloody worked?
我在酒吧时在你身上施的保护咒
The protection spell I cast on you at the bar.
你那是醉了在说胡话  才不是魔法
You were drunk and mumbling. That wasn't magic.
那是鬼扯
That was... pathetic.
你不懂  那咒语是个神话
No, you don't understand. That spell is a myth.
一个传说
A legend.
由大法师梅林为亚瑟王所创并亲自施放
Merlin created it and cast it at the behest of King Arthur.
任何受到咒语保护的圆桌骑士
If any Knight of the Round Table under that spell
如果与低阶骑士一同战死的话
was killed in the company of lesser knights,
他会吸收身边所有人的生命
he would absorb all the lives of those around him.
你想说什么
So what are you saying?
那咒语不仅救了你一命
That the spell not only saved your life,
还让你获得了火灾里其他死者的命
but you gained all the lives of those lost in the fire as well.
你是说我死不了
You're saying I can't die?
不  恰恰相反  你还是会死
No, on the contrary, you most certainly can die.
准确地说  是四十七次
47 times, to be precise.
你确定要这么做吗
You're sure you want to do this?
没错
Yeah.
我们终要与他一战  为何不在我们的地盘打
We either fight him on his ground or ours.
再说了  冒着生命危险的可不止我一个
Besides, I'm not the only one who's risking my life here.
查斯为我牺牲了很多
Chas has risked much more for me.
让我的挚友失望  会毁了我
Failing my best friend, that would ruin me.
但是你这里失败了  咱俩都完了
But failing you, that ruins us both.
那就别搞砸了
Then don't screw up.
咒语会立刻让你入睡
The spell will put you to sleep straightaway.
魇魔会感觉到
Karabasan will feel it.
当他进入圈中
When he enters the circle,
我就解除咒语  你滚出陷阱
I'll break the spell, you roll out of the trap,
然后我就点火
and I'll light it.
你最好说话算话
You better.
立刻沉睡吧[拉丁语]
Molles somnos, somno iam.
快啊
Come on.
现在  醒醒吧[拉丁语]
Nunc igitur consurge consurg.
做个好梦吧  你这丑陋的怪物
Sweet dreams, you ugly bastard.
都让开  别挡道
Clear the way. Coming through, people.
借过
Coming through.
情况越来越糟了  约翰
It's getting worse, John.
说点我不知道的行吗
Tell me something I don't know.
搞定了  查斯
It's done, Chas.
我们回去找浮士德
We're heading back to Faust.
可能需要你的帮助
We could use you as backup.
走吧
Let's do it.
等等  浮士德
Wait, Faust?
就是夺走我女儿灵魂的那人  对吗
That's the man that has my daughter's soul, isn't it?
我和你一起去
I'm coming with you.
这不是个好主意
Not a good idea.
听他的话吧  蕾妮  求你了
Listen to him, Renee. please.
他的话我听了很多年了
I have listened to him. for years.
全是约翰·康斯坦丁的丰功伟绩
Tall tales of John Constantine.
我一直听他的  直到最终害我们离婚收场
I listened to him until it tore us apart.
我要和你一起去
I'm coming with you.
能管管她吗  查斯
Deal with this, will you, Chas?
这是我的家庭  我的
This is my family. Mine.
我去外边等
I'll be outside.
你说得没错  是你的
You're right. it is.
但知道吗  当你女儿醒来的时候
But you know what? you-you got to be here
需要你在她身旁陪着她
for when your daughter wakes up.
好吗  我在这里陪你
Okay? I'll stay here with you.
求你了
Please.
带她回来
Bring her back.
她是我的一切
She's all I have.
我让你那魔鬼歇了
I put your sleep demon to bed.
现在该履行你的承诺了
A deal is a deal.
把女孩的灵魂交出来  浮士德
Let's have the girl's soul, Faust.
是的  我感觉到力量回来了
Yes, I felt the power return.
但是咱们的约定是将魔鬼赶回地狱
But our deal was to banish the beast to hell--
你却将它彻底毁灭了
you destroyed it by energy dispersion.
我们说好的  用恶魔换我女儿的灵魂
The deal was that demon for my daughter's soul.
我要改一下约定条款
I'm changing the terms of our agreement.
-约翰  -别
- John... - No.
这么多人的生命在你手中流逝
All those people wasting away by your hand as life passes them by.
你可不想死后落得这么个名声吧  菲力克斯
That is not the legacy you want, Felix.
你又懂什么
And what would you know of legacy?
自负  肮脏  乳臭未干的小子
A boastful, smutty, infantile boy.
靠着巧合和傲慢就学会了魔法
You create magic by accident and insolence,
而那些呕心沥血苦心钻研的人却得不到一点回报
while the truly devoted sweat and toil with no reward.
你永远不可能学会我的魔法  康斯坦丁
You'll never know my magic, Constantine.
但你会尝到我吃过的苦头
You will know my pain.
新的条件是什么  浮士德
What's the new price, Faust?
我们已经照你说的做了
We already paid his price.
再做一次  不然就跟你的女儿永别吧
And you'll pay it again or say good-bye to your daughter forever.
我们人就在这  挟持我女儿的人也在这  动手吧
We are here. The man who has my daughter is here. We act now.
你想要我怎么做
And what would you have me do?
使个伎俩  骗骗他  施个咒
A trick. A con. Cast a spell.
这些你都玩多少次了  随便什么都行
Pull something out of your ass like you always do.
睁开眼睛好好看看行吗
Open your eyes, will you?
如今浮士德占上风
Faust is still holding all the cards here.
我们不能总是被他牵制
We can't do this forever.
我女儿等不了这么久
My daughter does not have forever.
她的选择不多了
And she doesn't have many chances left,
但如今最有希望的仍然是我
but her best one still lies with me.
她已经信过你一次了
You've had your chance.
我把女儿的生命托付给你  你却失败了
And with my daughter's life at stake, you failed.
我见识过其他人在你失败后的下场
I've watched other people suffer the consequences of your action,
但这次是我的家人
but this is my family.
所以现在我说了算  不是你
So I'm gonna do things my way, not yours.
是吗  那你打算怎么办
Yeah? And how would you plan to do that?
我家人为你受的罪够多了
My family's suffered enough because of you.
生日快乐  亲爱的
Happy birthday, sweetie.
我买了你最喜欢的蛋糕  薄荷巧克力味的
I got you your favorite, mint chocolate chip.
对不起  我来晚了
I'm sorry I was late.
你不是来晚了
You weren't late.
你是错过了
You missed it.
我知道这听起来很疯狂
I-I know this sounds crazy,
但我必须得帮约翰干掉猴王
but I had to help John to slay the monkey king.
那怪物几乎把一家几口人活剥了
It tried to eviscerate an entire family.
我救了那孩子的命  却牺牲了我自己孩子的幸福
I saved the kids' lives, but I had to sacrifice my own's.
保护别人的家庭  这真的
Caring for another family, it's...
令人敬佩  查斯
Admirable, Chas.
但我们自己的家呢
But what about ours?
这占据了你的生活   也影响了我们的家庭
This is consuming your life, and it is poisoning ours.
47条人命没了  转到了我的身上
47 lives cut short and the balance left on mine.
我有责任让他们死得其所
It is my duty to make them count.
你唯一有责任的是我们
The only duty that you have is to us.
我理应有一个像样的丈夫
I deserve a husband.
你的女儿理应有一个像样的父亲
Your daughter deserves a father.
你需要好好关心一下你自己的家人
You need to start caring about your own family.
在你还有一个家的时候
While you still have one.
想找个更好的搭档吗
Looking for better company?
我知道给草包卖命是什么滋味
I know what it is to toil beneath lesser men.
你是来拍更佳搭档的马屁吗
Have you come to curry favor with a better one?
我可以拿32条灵魂跟你换我女儿的灵魂
I can give you 32 souls in exchange for my daughter's.
有意思  但你跟我一样是凡人
Intriguing. However, you're mortal like me,
我们只有一条灵魂
with only one soul to offer.
她的名字叫杰拉尔汀
Her name is Geraldine,
我以她的性命担保
And I'm telling you, on her life,
我这身体里还有其它32条灵魂
I'm carrying 32 souls inside this chassis.
我只看到...
The only thing I see...
一个绝望的可怜虫不惜说谎来拯救他的女儿
is a desperate, pathetic man lying to save his daughter.
现在  我要取走你的灵魂
Now I'm going to take your soul.
别这么着急
Not so fast.
我确实骗了你一件事
There's one thing I lied about.
经过这之后  我只能给你31条灵魂了
After this, I'll only have 31 souls left to offer.
布鲁克林的昏迷事件数量仍在增加
The number of coma cases is still spreading in Brooklyn,
迫使白思豪市长宣布
prompting mayor Bill de Blasio to declare New york
纽约进入公共卫生紧急状态
a public health emergency.
更多详情我们将在11点继续为您报道
More details coming up on our next report at 11:00.
医生说她的身体快不行了了
Her doctor said her body's shutting down.
事发的时候我就在家
I was home when it happened.
却没能保护她
I didn't protect her.
这事你也无能为力
There's nothing you could've done.
我知道你和查斯的关系并不是很好
I know everything isn't roses between you and Chas,
但如果他在这  他也会这么说的
But if he were here, he'd say the same.
当然了
Of course.
查斯这人简直体贴过了头
Chas is considerate to a fault.
尽管我和查斯关系不好  但还好我们有她
Things aren't roses between Chas and me, but we always had her.
她知道你在她身边
She knows you're here with her.
我生来...  就有通灵的能力
I'm a... a born psychic.
我能感受到一部分的她也在这里
I can feel part of her here with us.
等等  你是说你能跟她交流
Wait, can you communicate with her?
如果我能跟杰拉尔汀说上话
If i could just talk to Geraldine,
让她知道我在她身边就好了
if I could just let her know that I'm here.
她一定很害怕
She must be so scared.
我试试吧
I'll give it a shot.
好吧  你可以的
Okay. Okay.
你能做到的
Okay.
妈妈
Mommy?
是你吗
Is that you?
杰拉尔汀  我在这呢  宝贝
Geraldine. Geraldine. Geraldine, I'm right here, baby.
泽德  泽德  快醒醒
Zed. Zed! Zed, snap out... snap out of it.
快叫医生过来  泽德
We need a doctor in here! Zed!
让开点  没事的
Make way, make way. It's okay.
放松  没事的
Easy, now, easy.
能听到我吗
Can you hear me?
我们是来帮你的  告诉我发生什么事了
We're here to help. Tell me what's going on.
杰拉尔汀
哈斯金斯火车厂
橡园大道14030号  纽约
赶紧让辛医生过来  快
Get Dr. Shin in here, stat.
你确实是个言出必行的人
A man of your word, indeed.
我倒希望那是真的
I wish that were true.
如果你愿意将31条灵魂交给我  再加上你自己的
If you willingly commit 31 souls to me, including your own,
我就同意释放你女儿的灵魂
I agree to free your daughter's soul
让她回到自己的躯体中
and return it forthwith to her body,
并确保她有生之年不再骚扰她
where it shall remain safely until her natural death.
成交
Done.
法师之间才用得到血誓
The blood oath is for mages.
那我们就握个手吧
I'll settle for a handshake.
查斯
Chas!
别这么做
Don't do it.
如果你把那些灵魂连同自己的都交出去  你会死的
If you surrender those souls and yours, you will die.
不要啊
No!
我要改变约定条款
I'm changing the terms of our agreement.
你做了什么
What have you done?
今天我们一起死去
We both die today
但只有一个人能复活
and only one of us is coming back.
躲远点  约翰
Clear out, John!
你要这么做也行  伙计
Happy to do it your way, mate.
查斯
Chas!
-蕾妮  -你要做什么
- Renee? - What are you doing?
-救回我们的女儿  快跑  -趴下
- Saving our daughter. Run! - Get down!
我的老天
Oh, my... oh, my god.
天哪  天哪
Oh, my god! oh, my god!
没事的  亲爱的  没事的
You're all right, luv. You're all right.
不  我有事  我一点都不好
No, I'm not all right! It's not okay!
你看到他刚做了什么吗
Did you see what just happened to him?
他这么做很多次了  亲爱的  这就是他的工作
Many times, luv. Many times. This is what your husband does.
这就是他的能力
This is who he is.
都怪你
Because of you!
全都怪你
It's because of you!
都怪你
You!
很抱歉你得看见那些
Sorry you had to see that.
查斯的工作不是一般人能接受的
Chas's line of work is messy.
你的也是
So's yours.
查斯这么做会痛苦吗
Is it painful for Chas?
痛苦至极
Excruciating.
这个...  一般要多久
Uh, so how long does this take?
我是说...  他活过来
For him to-to return?
那要看死法有多惨烈了
Well, it depends on how violent the death.
但总有代价的
There's always a cost.
你学得倒挺快
You're learning.
我想让你知道
Now, look, for what it's worth,
我不是有意害你和查斯分手的
I never meant to get between you and Chas.
如果我可以回到过去改变一切
If I could go back and change it all,
我一定会的
I would.
可惜我做不到  但也因为如此  他才能活下来
But it's not in the cards, and because of it, he's alive.
许多人才能活下来
So are a lot of other people.
包括你们的女儿
Including your daughter.
她很快就会醒了
She'll be waking up soon.
你去守着她吧
You should go be with her.
蕾妮说她不再信任我了
Renee says I've broken her trust.
她要离开我  约翰
She's gonna leave me, John.
我不会让杰拉尔汀失去父亲
I won't let Geraldine grow up without a father.
你必须帮我逆转咒语  解决这问题
You have to reverse this spell. Fix this.
很抱歉  伙计  但我做不到
I'm really sorry, mate, but I can't.
我已经试了好几天了
I've been trying for days.
我没法这么活下去
I can't live like this.
你可以的
Yes, you can.
你可以选择把它当成是个包袱
You can shoulder this burden,
让内疚一点一点吞噬你
let it consume you from within.
也可以将这种能力纳为己用
Or you can wield it as you have.
来帮助我一起对抗邪恶
A weapon against evil by my side.
怎么决定在你  伙计
Whichever way you choose, mate,
不管决定是什么  我都会支持你
I'm with you every step of the way.
天哪  你活过来了
Oh, my god! You're alive.
你早就知道的
You knew I would be.
没错  但不是亲眼所见我还是不敢相信
Yeah, but seeing and knowing are two different things.
她在楼上
She's upstairs.
正等着你呢
Waiting for you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
爸爸
Daddy.
早啊  亲爱的
Hi, sweetheart.
妈妈说你早上会来
Mommy said you would be here in the morning,
我还不相信
but I didn't believe her.
虽然有时我答应来陪你却没有做到
I'm not always here for my weekends with you.
但我真的努力了  宝贝
But I always try, baby.
这是给我的吗
Is that for me?
我很喜欢
I love it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这下我们有一样的
Now we match.
我也有东西给你
I got something for you, too.
你要给我讲故事吗
Are you going to tell me a story?
可不止一个呢
I'm gonna tell you a few.
我想让你认识些我的朋友
I want to introduce you to some friends of mine.
我每天都将他们的照片带在身边
I carry them with me every day.
那是谁
Who's that?
她叫苏珊·史密斯
That is Susan Smith.
她是个护士
She was a nurse.
还是个母亲
And a mother.
她有两个跟你一样大的女儿
She had two little girls just your age.
我刚才怎么了
What happened to me?
你晕过去了  亲爱的
You blew a fuse, luv.
将灵魂这么暴露在灵体世界是件很危险的事
You know, it's not safe to bare your soul to the spirit world.
那需要多年的训练
It takes years of training.
你为什么要这么做  傻姑娘
So why the bloody hell did you do it, you silly sod?
一个小女孩的灵魂
A little girl was...
被一个疯老头挟持了
at the mercy of a mad man.
你终于肯敞开心扉了  这是好事
You're opening up. That's great.
但也别操之过急  好吗
Just, uh, don't open so soon, yeah?
都听你的  约翰
Whatever you say, John.
还有一件事
One more thing.
是关于你母亲的
About your mother.
我母亲怎么了
What about my mother?
她说别为她的死而自责
She said her death wasn't your fault.
你见到我母亲了
You saw my mother.
泽德
Zed?